moviemaker.com 2017-10-01

# Privacy Policy - MovieMaker Magazine

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and how we safeguard your information.

 _The Information We Collect_ :

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the moviemakermagazine.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials.

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New York festival ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing camera ads to someone who frequents camera retail sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 _The Way We Use Information_ :

We use the information you provide in newsletter registration and subscriptions only to complete that request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

In terms of the information collected for site and _MovieMaker_ Magazine subscriptions, we use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 _Our Commitment To Data Security_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We do not, nor have we ever stored credit card information. Those processes are managed by third party providers with data security safeguards in place.

 _How To Contact Us_

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at assistant@moviemaker.com.
